(Amy:)Sometimes I think it might be
nice to have one.
(Howard:)Really?
(Amy:)Not for sex, for convenience.
(Amy:)You can't deny that,
by comparison,
(Amy:)our internal plumbing
is extremely high maintenance.
(Penny:)Again, I've never given
it much thought.
(Amy:)We have time now.
(Amy:)Think about it.
(Bernadette:)Oh, good.
(Penny:)Hey.
(Bernadette:)Can I stay here tonight?
(Penny:)Yeah. Why, what happened?
(Bernadette:)Howard's a complete
and total ass.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah, that.
Come on in.
(Bernadette:)Thanks. I'll sleep
on the floor.
(Amy:)Not necessary.
(Amy:)Penny and I are perfectly
comfortable sharing a bed.
(Penny:)We are?
(Amy:)Of course, we're best friends.
(Penny:)Oh, right, right, the blog.
(Amy:)Word of warning, though.
(Amy:)I'm prone to night terrors,
so when I wake up kicking
and screaming, don't panic.
(Amy:)Just pin me down and stroke
my hair, and I'll be fine.